J: Another hour!
A: Are you also on the London flight?
J: Yes, unfortunately.
Another delay.
Who knows when we’ll take off…
A: Is there someone waiting for you at the airport?
J: No… that’s probably a good thing
A: No, me neither.
I’m Alex, by the way.
You’re British, right? Do you live in London?
J: I’m Jake.
No, I don’t live in the UK, I live in Chicago now.
I work at Chicago State University.
A: Oh, cool.
So why are you going to London?
J: I’m going to give a talk at a conference in Oxford, actually.
A: So do you like living in Chicago?
J: Oh, I love it.
I’m going to stay there for at least another two years – they’ve extended my contract.
A: Yeah, Chicago’s a great city.
I’m not working, I’m on holiday.
I’m going to do a tour of the UK.
And I’m going to visit Oxford!
J: Oh right.
That’s er, that’s nice.
A: I’m really excited.
It’s my first trip to England.
J: Well, I’m sure you’re going to have a great time.
May’s a great month to be in the UK.
A: I hope so.
Hey, maybe you could show me around Oxford University? Are you going to be there all week?
J: Oh, well… I’m going to be very busy, but maybe…
A: So your trip is all work, no fun?
J: Yes – though, well, I’m going to meet up with a friend, well,
my ex-girlfriend really, who I was with when I was a student.
She lives in Oxford now.
A: That’s great!
J: Yeah, we broke up when I got the job in Chicago, but, well…
I’m really looking forward to seeing her.
A: Hey, we’re probably not going to leave for some time.
Let’s have a drink somewhere.
J: Um, OK, yes, why not?
Let’s check the Departures screen first.
A: Oh – Jake – is this yours?
J: My phone! Thanks.
Typical me, I always lose things when I’m travelling.
A: So, text me your number, now, so you don’t forget…